bestnetentcasino.info 2019-06-30

# Privacy policy for users of bestnetentcasino.info

﻿

Details 
     Last Updated: 04 January 2019 

BESTNETENTCASINO.INFO PRIVACY AND COOKIES POLICY

At [https://bestnetentcasino.info](https://bestnetentcasino.info/) (“BestNetentcasino.info“, “we“, “us“), we process personal data about our customers and visitors on our websites (“you“). We make efforts to handle your data with care, keep it secure and comply with data protection laws.

## How this Policy Works

The purpose of this Policy is to explain when, why and how we process information which may relate to you (“personal data“). It also provides important information on your statutory rights. This Policy is not intended to override the terms of any contract you have with us, nor rights you might have under data protection laws.

## Who is responsible for looking after your data?

You should be aware that although we are principally responsible for looking after your data, information may be held in databases which can be accessed by other companies. When accessing your data, all companies will comply with the standards set out in this Policy.

## What personal data do we process?

We may process the following personal data about you:

  * Name
  * Date of birth
  * Email address
  * Password
  * IP address
  * Location data
  * Website usage
  * Gender
  * Age
  * Occupation
  * Personal preferences and opinions

## What do we use your data for and when do we process your personal data?

Bestnetentcasino.info will collect information directly from you when you use our services or visit our websites.

We use your data to:

  * Send out promotional emails relating to products and services.
  * Analyse information in our systems and databases to improve the way we run our business and websites according to user preferences, to provide a better service and user experience.
  * Improve and target advertisements that you receive from us.
  * Register you for a chat forum or community, if we make available, in which you can provide comments.
  * Meet or exercise any of our legal obligations or rights

## Who do we share your personal data with?

We work with many third parties, to help manage our business and deliver services. These third parties may from time to time need to have access to your data:

  * Our mailing application provider Aweber Systems, Inc., based in the USA, who is Privacy Shield certified as you may see here and processes personal data on our behalf;
  * Our plugin provider and host of Joomla.com processes personal data on our behalf;
  * Our hosting provider cloudflare.com processes personal data on our behalf;
  * Our analytics service providers (such as Google, Hotjar and VWO), who process personal data for their purposes as Data Controllers. Please refer to our Cookie Policy in the Appendix below to identify how you may prevent access to your personal data by analytics providers.
  * Service providers or data processors that handle your personal data on our instructions, for example, cloud services.
  * If we are under a duty to disclose, to comply with a legal obligation or protect our interests or security.
  * In the event, we sell, buy or re-organise any business or assets, or if our assets are acquired by a third party, including prospective sellers or buyers.

## International Transfers

  * International Transfers means that personal data is transferred to a country outside the European Union.
  * As set out above, we may allow access to your data to third parties who may be located outside the European Union.
  * We may also disclose your data if we receive a legal or regulatory request from a foreign law enforcement body outside the European Union.
  * We will always take steps to ensure that any international transfer of information is managed to protect your rights and interests. Any requests for information that we receive from law enforcement or regulators will be carefully checked before personal data is disclosed.

## Direct Marketing

  * We will use your data to send you direct marketing communications regarding products and services that we offer and our partners offer regarding for example online casino, sports betting and financial services. This may be in the form of email or targeted online advertisements.
  * In some cases, our processing of your personal data for marketing purposes will be based on our legitimate interests (see above). When required by law it will be based on your consent.
  * You always have a right to say no to further direct marketing, at any time. You can use the opt-out link that you find in all direct marketing communications, or by contacting us.
  * We take steps to limit direct marketing to a reasonable and proportionate level and to send you communications that we believe may be of interest or relevance to you, based on the information we have about you.

## How long do we keep your personal data?

  * We will retain your data for as long as reasonably necessary for the purposes listed of this Policy.
  * In some circumstances, we keep your personal data during a certain period to meet for example legal, tax or accounting requirements.
  * We maintain a data retention policy for personal data in our care. Where your personal data is no longer required we will ensure it is either securely deleted or made anonymous.

## What are your rights?

You have some rights about your data. More information about each of these rights can be found by referring to the table set out further below. To exercise your rights, you may contact us as by sending an email to [[email protected]](https://bestnetentcasino.info/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

### Please note the following if you wish to exercise your rights

You can ask us to:- confirm whether we are processing your data;

  * Give you a copy of that data;
  * Provide you with other information about your data, for example, what data we have, what we use it for, who we disclose it to, whether we transfer it outside the EU and how we protect it. How long we keep it for, what rights you have, how you can make a complaint, where we got your data from and whether we have carried out any Automated Decision Making or Profiling, to the extent that information has not already been provided to you in this Policy.
  * Rectification You can ask us to rectify inaccurate personal data. We may seek to verify the accuracy of the data before rectifying it.

### Erasure You can ask us to erase your data, but only where

  * it is no longer needed for the purposes for which it was collected; or
  * you have withdrawn your consent (where processing was based on consent); or
  * following a successful right to object (see ‘Objection’ below); or
  * it has been processed unlawfully; or
  * to comply with a legal obligation.

### We are not required to comply with your request to erase your personal data if the processing of your data is necessary

  * for compliance with a legal obligation; or
  * for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims;
  * There are certain other circumstances in which we are not required to comply with your erasure request, although these two are the most likely circumstances in which we would deny that request.
  * Restriction You can ask us to restrict (i.e. keep but not use) your data, but only where:- its accuracy is contested (see Rectification), to allow us to verify its accuracy; or
  * the processing is unlawful, but you do not want it erased; or
  * it is no longer needed for the purposes for which it was collected, but we still need it to establish, exercise or defend legal claims; or
  * You have exercised the right to object, and verification of overriding grounds is pending. We can continue to use your data following a request for a restriction, where:- we have your consent; or
  * to establish, exercise or defend legal claims; or
  * to protect the rights of another natural or legal person.
  * Portability You can ask us to provide your data to you in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format, or you can ask to have it ‘ported’ directly to another Data Controller, but in each case only where:
  * the processing is based on your consent or the performance of a contract with you; and
  * the processing is carried out by automated means.  
Objection You can object to any processing of your data which has our ‘legitimate interests’ as its legal basis if you believe your fundamental rights and freedoms outweigh our legitimate interests.
  * We have an opportunity to demonstrate that we have compelling legitimate interests which override your rights and freedoms.  
International Transfers You can ask to obtain a copy of, or reference to, the safeguards under which your data is transferred outside of the European Economic Area.
  * We may redact data transfer agreements or related documents (i.e. certain obscure information contained within these documents) for reasons of commercial sensitivity.  
Supervisory Authority You have a right to complain about the responsible local supervisory authority about our processing of your data.
  * We ask that you, please attempt to resolve any issues with us first, although you have a right to contact your supervisory authority at any time.

### Cookie Policy

  * We use Cookies. To offer you a full range of functions when you visit our website, recognise your preferences, and make the use of our site more comfortable and convenient, we use “cookies.”
  * What are Cookies? A cookie, pixel or similar technology is a small file or information saved on your computer or device when you visit the website. It enables the site to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size, and other display preferences) over a period, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another.

### Your options

  * By using our website, you agree to the use and storage of cookies on your computer or device.
  * You can generally view our website without cookies, but certain parts of the site may not work properly or navigate be slower.
  * If you do not wish cookies to be stored on your computer or device, you can deactivate the relevant option in the system settings of your browser. You can also delete stored cookies in the system settings of your browser at any time.
  * More information on how to deactivate or delete cookies can be found here: https://www.aboutcookies.org/cookie-faq/. However, please keep in mind that if you do not accept any cookies, this may restrict the functionality of our offerings.

### Categories of cookies

We use cookies for different purposes and with various functions.

### Some cookies are

  * necessary in technical terms (technical necessity)
  * stored and used for a certain period (storage duration)
  * placed and stored by us or a third party (cookie provider).

### Technical necessity

Cookies that are technical:

  * Necessary: We use certain cookies because they are strictly required for the website and its functions to work correctly. These cookies are automatically placed on your computer or device when you access the website or a specific function unless you have set your browser to reject cookies.  
Not necessary: Cookies that are not strictly necessary are placed on your computer or device to improve convenience and performance of our website or save specific settings that you have made. We also use cookies that are not strictly necessary in technical terms to get information on the frequency of use of specific areas of our website, so that we can adapt to your needs and requirements on a more targeted basis.

### Storage duration

  * Session cookies: Some cookies are only needed for the period of your website session, so-called “session cookies”. They will be erased or become invalid as soon as you leave our website or your current session expires. Session cookies are used, for example, to retain certain information during your session.
  * Permanent cookies: Some cookies are stored for a longer period. For example, it allows us to recognise you when you re-access our website at a later time, and access saved settings. As a result, you can access web pages faster or with greater convenience, for example, that you do not need to set certain options again, such as your chosen language. Permanent cookies are automatically deleted after a predefined period.
  * Flow cookies: These cookies are used for communication between our internal servers within our company group. They are placed on your computer or device when you started navigating the website and deleted after the end of your navigation on the website. Flow cookies are given a unique identification number but do not allow us to draw any conclusions regarding the actual customer or user.

### Cookie providers

  * Provider cookies: These are cookies are placed by us or the operator of our website, who is commissioned by us.
  * Third-party cookies: “Third-party cookies” are stored and used by other organisations or websites, for example, Web analytics tools. External providers may also use cookies to display advertising or to integrate content from social networks, such as social plugins. For further information on Web analytics tools and measurement of reach, please see below in this cookie policy.

### Use of cookies for Web analytics and reach measurement

We use Google Analytics, a Web analytics service of Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies to identify the frequency of use of certain areas of our website and to identify preferences. The information regarding your use of this website that is generated by the cookie (including your truncated IP address) is transferred to a Google server in the United States and stored there. Google will use this information to analyse your use of the website, compile reports on website activity for us, and perform further services associated with website use and Internet use. Google may also transmit this information to third parties where required by law or to the extent third parties process these data on behalf of Google.

You can deactivate Google Analytics using a browser add-on if you do not wish the website analysis to take place. You can download the add-on here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=.

This add-on stores “opt-out” information on your device that serves to match up your deactivation of Google Analytics. Please note that this kind of “opt out” only leads to the deactivation of Google Analytics for the device and browser from which the opt-out was activated. Also, you may need to reactivate it if you delete cookies from your device.

If you want to know more about privacy politics of bestnetentcasino.info or have questions about our cookie policy, feel free to contact us via [[email protected]](https://bestnetentcasino.info/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
